export const set5 = [
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">33</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">-</span>6</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["21", "27", "24", "30"],
    answer: "27"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">64</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">-</span>8</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["56", "52", "59", "50"],
    answer: "56"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">47</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">-</span>9</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["34", "40", "38", "36"],
    answer: "38"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">52</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">-</span>8</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["46", "44", "40", "48"],
    answer: "44"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">35</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">-</span>7</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["28", "26", "20", "24"],
    answer: "28"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">56</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">-</span>8</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["42", "50", "48", "46"],
    answer: "48"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">46</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">-</span>4</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["40", "38", "42", "44"],
    answer: "42"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">83</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">-</span>7</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["76", "70", "72", "78"],
    answer: "76"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">63</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">-</span>7</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["52", "58", "56", "50"],
    answer: "56"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">73</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">-</span>4</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["67", "71", "69", "65"],
    answer: "69"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">44</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">-</span>7</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["39", "35", "33", "31"],
    answer: "37"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">41</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">-</span>7</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["36", "32", "38", "34"],
    answer: "34"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">45</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">-</span>9</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["34", "38", "36", "32"],
    answer: "36"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">86</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">-</span>8</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["80", "76", "78", "74"],
    answer: "78"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">93</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">-</span>6</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["87", "85", "89", "83"],
    answer: "87"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">48</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">-</span>4</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["42", "46", "40", "44"],
    answer: "44"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">57</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">-</span>8</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["49", "47", "51", "45"],
    answer: "49"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">43</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">-</span>8</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["33", "37", "31", "35"],
    answer: "35"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">48</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">-</span>9</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["37", "41", "39", "35"],
    answer: "39"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">42</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">-</span>9</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["35", "31", "33", "37"],
    answer: "33"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">49</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">-</span>6</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["45", "41", "47", "43"],
    answer: "43"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">43</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">-</span>7</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["38", "34", "36", "32"],
    answer: "36"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">46</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">-</span>9</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["35", "39", "37", "41"],
    answer: "37"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">41</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">-</span>8</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["35", "31", "37", "33"],
    answer: "33"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">40</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">-</span>6</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["36", "32", "34", "38"],
    answer: "34"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">34</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">-</span>6</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["30", "26", "28", "32"],
    answer: "28"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">83</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">-</span>7</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["72", "78", "74", "76"],
    answer: "76"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">56</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">-</span>6</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["48", "50", "46", "52"],
    answer: "50"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">51</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">-</span>6</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["47", "43", "45", "41"],
    answer: "45"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">48</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">-</span>9</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["41", "37", "39", "35"],
    answer: "39"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">72</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">-</span>6</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["64", "68", "66", "70"],
    answer: "66"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">63</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">-</span>7</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["56", "52", "58", "54"],
    answer: "56"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">43</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">-</span>6</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["39", "35", "37", "33"],
    answer: "37"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">42</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">-</span>7</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["33", "37", "35", "31"],
    answer: "35"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">36</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">-</span>8</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["30", "26", "28", "24"],
    answer: "28"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">82</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">-</span>6</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["74", "78", "76", "72"],
    answer: "76"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">63</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">-</span>7</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["58", "54", "56", "52"],
    answer: "56"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">73</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">-</span>5</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["66", "70", "68", "64"],
    answer: "68"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">46</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">-</span>8</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["40", "36", "38", "34"],
    answer: "38"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">76</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">-</span>9</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["69", "65", "67", "63"],
    answer: "67"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">63</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">-</span>8</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["57", "53", "55", "51"],
    answer: "55"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">46</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">-</span>9</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["39", "35", "37", "41"],
    answer: "37"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">43</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">-</span>5</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["36", "40", "38", "34"],
    answer: "38"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">61</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">-</span>8</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["55", "51", "53", "57"],
    answer: "53"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">65</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">-</span>7</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["60", "56", "58", "54"],
    answer: "58"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">41</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">-</span>6</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["37", "33", "35", "31"],
    answer: "35"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">58</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">-</span>9</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["51", "47", "49", "45"],
    answer: "49"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">83</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">-</span>7</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["74", "78", "76", "72"],
    answer: "76"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">38</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">-</span>9</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["31", "27", "29", "25"],
    answer: "29"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">26</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">-</span>7</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["21", "17", "19", "15"],
    answer: "19"
  }
];